am i all right I alive I am going to be
live five to ten minutes a day or doing
it on the iPad okay and what's available
to me at that moment in time what is
available to me when I feel the urge to
actually go on and speak from my heart
and so today I watched teal swans video
on hierarchy actually watched it twice
so watched it once while I was doing
something else and it was of course
triggering me I heard she's one of my
big wounds it's what I'm here to
dismantle so of course it was was
informative and also exactly what I
needed to watch right now so first of
all in her field
I absolutely recognized that table Swan
is a superior entity to me that that is
why I am reading her book and Dylan
collegian process it's ironic that while
I'm reading the completion process I'm
also realizing that to a much lesser
degree I this is what I've been doing
but on a very slow not systematic
wouldn't be able to explain it to
anybody else process of accepting myself
of loving myself listening to my
emotions and learning from them
individually so that I can become live
into what I'm here to do and so that is
why I have the completion process even
though reading it it's a whole other
video to discuss me at my reading skills
but reading good times one of my loves
they got taken away with diverting
damage but I'm doing it even if I have
to take three naps a day to read it so I
wanted to discuss some of the things
that she says in it this people are you
know outside right now I love but as
soon as he hit record the universe's
like how about there's no no I love it
okay
work through it sensory processing so
she talks about how we have wounds in
the past of not being taken into
consideration and that's absolutely my
rooms with hierarchy I have a difference
and that we you look like an idiot when
you don't accept Authority and I get
that that's exactly what happens with me
in a medical system is it's not that I
don't accept that doctors have more
knowledge that I do on medicine and on
the human body as a whole it's that I
don't think they have superior knowledge
on my body because they're not in it
so they can only deal with statistics
they can only deal with most people
should do it this way
they haven't had enough had the
experience time and time again of
listening to them and happy to go
horribly awry and then beat in the same
position of being like we're not doing
it that way this works and they don't
accept my authority on my own body
because they don't accept Authority on
my home body they need they need to be
in a position of hierarchy so it's not
that I don't understand it superiority
is a thing I'm not going on the street
and asking anyone to be my neurosurgeon
I want one of the best neurosurgeons to
cut me open but when it's on my body
I should have authority on my body so
they should be able to explain it to me
and I should be able to choose and I
also fully admit that I have wounds in
this area that is partly why I'm doing
the completion process so I can I can
tackle my position on this planet my
genius on this planet what I'm here to
be on a platform for for the greater
good and not do it from a place of ego
and wound but she also talked about each
one of us being like a part of an engine
and so depending on what your needs are
what the cards needs are different items
have a hierarchy in the moment and I
totally think that as a that is how we
come together and save this planet is by
honoring our own unique individual
selves and what we're here to do and
organizing that together through
technology which is what I mean by
bringing down the hierarchy is not
bringing down superiority not bringing
out that some people are better at
things than other people but that
doesn't make you a more worthy human
being that makes you a lucky human being
that means you're here to give that
that's its own reward
so that is a piece of it that I'm still
working out but my issue is in my own
life I've never been a full-piece I've
never been a piston or a fuel gauge it's
like I'm like 80% of a fuel gauge and
80% of a piston and I can't do what
society is like here are these job
descriptions and you fit into this one
or you fit into this one and a lot of
times the hierarchy is that like who
decides who gets into medical school the
people who already been through Medical
School so if you think outside of the
box you're not going to get into medical
school if you have
disability is going to be much more
difficult for you to get into medical
school so the medical system is filled
with people who are neurotypical some
interneural divers for sure and people
who've had to have a healthy life
because you can't be in med school and
not and going through chronic illness
it's really difficult and so there is
this issue I have with her with
authority that I can't trust somebody in
a position of power over me who has less
knowledge than I do and with a doctor is
very much although in medicine what
they've trained in they have more
information but I often have more
information in nutrition definitely in
cellular biology in genetics in my field
of expertise that I went to school for
and I only did an undergrad and yet I
have more interaction I of course have
more information of my own body
there is this phenomenon that happens
the more intelligent people are the more
they know what they don't know so so I
spent four years a university and that
really just like showed me everything I
didn't know other people look at a
university degree is like a pedestal and
I look at it is like that's just arty
that's a kindergarten it's the
kindergarten of being a scientist and so
I know everything that I don't know but
I also know that I know a hell of a lot
more than most people including people
that aren't necessarily in science of
people who um can't admit that they
think they know everything about
everything you look at somebody who
comes from place of ego like in my
opinion Trump and says he's the best at
everything I'm like I think I'm better
than you in basically every area but I
can acknowledge my inferiority but in so
doing they're like right so I'm in a
peer of superiority no no you're not if
you can admit what you don't know and
what you're not good at I can't trust
you to tell me what you are good at and
yet as a society we very much look at
when someone says they're inferior
they're like oh you must be inferior
everywhere right you show up on a first
date as your authentic self we think Inc
all your quirks you're negative you're
positive all of it they're like oh
if you're like this on day one you must
be hiding this is a nice bird you must
be hiding the 90% Ernie's I can't
imagine what its gonna be like in 3
months you're like oh this is what
you're getting three months from now
three seconds from now I'm gonna change
back and forth I'm gonna tend to human
being but
this is what you're getting but they
don't know that because we know that on
first day it's yours to show up as a
fake version of yourself so I'm going
into what should have been things but I
love like the just somebody what do you
do if you're not a full piston there's
still advice there my pedestal is
binding people even if you're not a full
piston you still have a place in this
world because someone else is the 10%
that you're not and doing what is easy
for you and giving that to the world is
all you have to do and everyone is to
have their position of genius end and a
pedestal in that regard but I don't like
the idea that some outside authority has
control of my life or some outside
authority that has their own hierarchy
and their own agenda gets to decide who
is in a position of authority who is
ranked better and worse not based on
whether they actually are better or
worse but based on their your cousin
based on they have more money based on
whatever the actual power dynamics of
deciding the power context so she did
talk about three things then and
remember the three I just brought three
things three things about hierarchy that
is like this is I think a healthy
hierarchy and it was when you're in a
position of authority bringing love into
it and taking all things as parts of
yourself and that I got I have that on
the other side of the spectrum where
it's possibly even too much and I have
to rein that back in uber empathy and it
has cost me on this planet and I'm
figuring out peace out awareness a
higher consciousness and more sense that
when you're aware of course you're
coming from you place by your conscious
and more sense things to get we try and
transcend prejudice and ignorance and to
me that's just constantly seeking it out
to know that I'm never gonna be fully
I'm ignorant because you can't be you
can't know everything one human being
can that's why I want to have the system
that allows everyone to put in their
genius and us all to have access to the
pool of genius individual yes yes and I
love the teal Swan comes up exactly what
I'm here to do but for a completely
different like she downloaded it from
somewhere else it has access I'm like I
also but from a logical side but I can't
articulate and explain it like she does
but my
purpose on this planet is completely
different than hers and yet very similar
yes
but the individual that we have to start
allowing people to be their own
individual superior selves and I think
together we can create the tools and the
systems to be able to easily help people
find that and to be able to match the
pieces together so that if you are a
piston you can find the fuel gauge and
the other I felt like she picks
analogies that I don't know like I was
gonna say one of the things chucks it
was the surfer what's his name I can't
remember Laird Hamilton and how of
course if you are an amateur surfer you
might be giving him advice when he does
not need that in any way shape or form
because he's it he's the best surfer on
the planet I know so little about
surfing in the ocean but it's hard for
me to come up with an analogy to but my
analogy which honestly I think servers
would serve it anyway is like I might
not be in a position of authority over
surfing but what if I see something he
doesn't right what if I see a shark must
be like well he might have seen it too
right I'm not gonna tell him about it
and that is what higher he does often in
our in our society is that because it's
the boss you can't go to the boss with a
problem when you do order the boss that
problem you're penalized because you saw
the problem but you don't necessarily
have a solution the system I want to
create together is one where everybody
is able anybody is able to say what the
problem is and other people able to come
up with a solution because that is us
looking for our individual genius
finding the pieces that we are some
people are great at pointing out
problems they're never gonna be the ones
who solve it
other people are amazing at solving
problems but they don't necessarily per
see the problem and some people can do
both we need to be able to create the
system that we all get to give our
genius and all give our platform thank
you please like and subscribe if you are
watching this I'm gonna be on more often
the universe has given me a clear
indication this is where I am supposed
to be so I will be coming on here and
practicing splash doing speaking for my
heart instead of my brain where I am
more easy it is easier for me to
articulate then when I'm trying to get
you to understand it when I speak for my
heart I just want to say what I'm here
to say I do a better job and I'm here to
serve the universe and serve my purpose
on the planet so
I am going to act in the best way I'm
capable which this is I can record a
video live I can come on YouTube I can
put myself out there because I've done
the work that this is easy and fun for
me so hopefully it gets somewhere and if
not I'm just gonna enjoy the process
along the way thank you